The Battle is over. The War has just begun!
Puppet Master X: Axis Rising is a horror, war, science
fiction film directed by Charles Band.
After foiling a plan to blow up an American arms plant, Danny and Beth quickly find that one of Toulon's puppets has been
kidnapped by the Nazis, and his life-giving serum has been synthesized to create a master race of unstoppable soldiers.
Danny, played by Kip Canyon.
Beth, played by Jean Louise O'Sullivan.
Freuhoffer, played by Oto Brezina.
Uschi, played by Stephanie Sanditz.
Sgt. Stone, played by Brad Potts.
Ozu, played by Terumi Shimazu.
Puppet Master X: Axis Rising is a 2012 American horror film and is
the tenth entry in the Puppet Master film series.
Produced and directed by Charles Band, it is a direct sequel to 2010's Puppet Master: Axis of Evil and introduces
new puppets named Blitzkrieg, Bombshell, Kamikaze, and Weremacht, who fight alongside the Nazis.
Puppet Master X: Axis Rising was released on
October 9, 2012 by Full Moon Features.
A sequel, Puppet Master: Axis Termination, was released in 2017.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.